How are you feeling?
你感觉怎么样?
Great. Never better.
Great. 从来没这么好过.
Aren't you suffering from jet lag?
难道你没有时差反应?
Oh no.Besides,the afternoon meeting only lasted...What?...four hours?
Oh no.而且,下午的会只开了…… 什么? ……4个小时?
Yes,but we have another one early tomorrow morning.
Yes, 但明天一早我们还有一个会.
It will last all day.
要开一整天.
We won't finish till six o'clock.
我们到晚上6点才能结束.
Hm.
Are you worried about getting tired?
你会担心很累吗?
No.I wanted to do some shopping tomorrow.
No. 我原打算明天买点儿东西.
How late is Sogo open?
Sogo百货商场开到几点?
Quite late.
相当晚.
But don't forget,there is a banquet for you tomorrow night.
但不要忘了, 明天晚上有欢迎你的宴会.
Ah.How long does that last?
Ah. 那会多久?
They can take hours.
可能要好几个小时.
I'm afraid you won't be back at your hotel at least until midnight.
恐怕你至少也要到半夜才能回饭店.
Maybe later.
也许更晚.
Oh well.
Wait...Sogo's is open tonight,isn't it?
Wait...Sogo今天晚上也开,是吗?
Yes.
Well,can we go now?
Well, 我们现在去行吗?
Of course.The tram will take about thirty minutes.
Of course. 乘电车大约30分钟就到了.
A taxi will be faster.
坐出租车去更快.
Let's walk.It's a beautiful evening.
我们步行去吧. 夜色这么好.
I am amazed you're still going!
我太吃惊了, 你还能继续走!